<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-06T09:59:25.524-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
        cq:template="/conf/abbvie-com2/settings/wcm/templates/secondary-tertiary-page-template"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-06T09:59:25.508-04:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="New report reveals urgent need to address ovarian cancer burden in australia"
        jcr:uuid="d3c730fb-c9a6-4878-907e-d8b1349fd3e3"
        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/remotepage"
        ctaAltText="Learn more"
        ctaText="Learn more"
        eyebrow="23 November 2025"
        navTitle="New report reveals urgent need to address ovarian cancer burden in australia"
        pageTitle="New report reveals urgent need to address ovarian cancer burden in australia"
        title="New report reveals urgent need to address ovarian cancer burden in Australia">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
            <responsivegrid
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                <experiencefragmentHeader
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T02:38:48.573-05:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/au/en/site/header/australia-header-english"/>
                <responsivegrid1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                    <container
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835859,1653545825683,1653545847150,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T09:01:04.798-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#071D49"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset"/>
                    <container2
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545825685,1653242825678,1653545835860]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#FFFFFF">
                        <container3
                            cq:styleIds="[1653545835982,1653545835879,1653242825678,1653545847150,1653545825686]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                            <breadcrumb
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/breadcrumb/v2/breadcrumb"
                                disableShadowing="false"
                                hideCurrent="false"
                                showHidden="true"
                                startLevel="4"/>
                            <title
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1661545829678,1651545825691]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T03:07:49.526-05:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="New Report Reveals Urgent Need to Address Ovarian Cancer Burden in Australia"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                type="h1"
                                variant="h"/>
                            <text
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-10T02:48:24.646-05:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>A new report released today reveals the far-reaching impact of ovarian cancer on women, affecting their relationships, roles at home and work, physical and mental health, and highlights the urgent need to improve outcomes.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>&amp;nbsp;Ovarian cancer is one of the least understood cancers affecting women and is associated with high mortality rates.&lt;sup>1&lt;/sup>&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Less than half of women with ovarian cancer survive beyond five years, lagging well behind average survival rates for all female cancers.&lt;sup>2&lt;/sup>&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </container3>
                    </container2>
                    <container_1286594283
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545825686,1653545847150,1653545835982]"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2025-10-03T13:34:51.099-04:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-10-03T13:39:30.646-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset">
                        <grid
                            jcr:created="{Date}2025-10-03T13:34:59.923-04:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-10-03T13:35:25.247-04:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/grid/v2/grid"
                            rowCount="1">
                            <columns jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                                <item0
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    columnWidth="1"
                                    dataPriority="1"/>
                                <item1
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    columnWidth="10"
                                    dataPriority="1"/>
                                <item2
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    columnWidth="1"
                                    dataPriority="1"/>
                            </columns>
                            <par_12
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                                <text
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-10-03T13:35:54.680-04:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-10T03:14:45.388-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA (23 November 2025)&lt;/b> – Ovarian cancer is one of the most challenging and least understood cancers affecting women in Australia today, impacting not only their health but also the very fabric of personal lives, relationships and families.&lt;sup>1&lt;/sup> Despite being the ninth most common cancer in females, ovarian cancer is the fifth leading cause of cancer death among females.&lt;sup>2,3 &lt;/sup>Tragically, fewer than half of women diagnosed survive beyond five years and ovarian cancer survival rates remain lower than the average for all female cancers.&lt;sup>2&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>In addition to the devastating impacts on the lives of those diagnosed, a new report launched today highlights the significant economic and social burden of ovarian cancer in Australia, while underscoring the opportunity to improve outcomes for women. The Value of Hope: Addressing the burden of ovarian cancer in Australia report, developed by Deloitte Access Economics in partnership with AbbVie, found advances in care and support for women with ovarian cancer have the potential to improve quality of life and help women maintain their important roles in families, communities, and the economy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“Ovarian cancer is a difficult cancer to diagnose and treat. Despite multiple clinical trials, we have not identified an effective screening strategy that will allow for early detection of ovarian cancer and the majority of patients have advanced disease at presentation. For patients where the cancer recurs, we have no cure. Our care needs to be tailored for each patient with the aim of providing the most efficacious treatment while maintaining quality of life.” – Dr. Michelle Harrison, Medical Oncologist, Chris O’Brien Lifehouse.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>The report highlights the pressing challenges facing the community, impacting outcomes for women and their families in Australia:&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>1.&lt;b> Late diagnosis means delayed treatment with less chance of success.&lt;/b> With no early detection test available, two-thirds of women are diagnosed with ovarian cancer at an advanced stage.&lt;sup>4&lt;/sup> By this point, treatment is more challenging, and chances of survival are drastically reduced.&lt;sup>5&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>2. &lt;b>Treatment options are limited, and resistance and recurrence are common.&lt;/b> For decades, platinum-based chemotherapy has been the standard first-line treatment for ovarian cancer.&lt;sup>6&lt;/sup> Yet around one in four women develop resistance and a staggering four in five with advanced disease see their cancer return leaving few options at this stage.&lt;sup>7&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>3. &lt;b>Barriers in accessing diagnostics, testing and personalised care.&lt;/b> In addition to limited early screening, patients often lack consistent access to testing after diagnosis, which is essential for guiding targeted treatment.&lt;sup>8&lt;/sup> The issue is further compounded for women living in non-metropolitan regions, who can face reduced access to specialised healthcare providers and a lack of local medical services.&lt;sup>9&amp;nbsp;&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Economic fallout of ovarian cancer&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The report demonstrates that ovarian cancer affects not just lives, but also livelihoods, by exploring both the broader economic impact and the personal financial impact on individuals. Ovarian cancer costs the Australian health system $270.9 million per year, with the majority of cost being on public hospitals, the Pharmaceutical Benefits Scheme and private healthcare.&lt;sup>10&lt;/sup> The relatively higher proportions of late-stage diagnoses and high recurrence rates mean ovarian cancer incurs much higher costs than other cancers.&lt;sup>10&lt;/sup> An ovarian cancer diagnosis leads many women to reduce their participation in the workforce while managing treatment, contributing to an annual loss of $42.5 million in labour productivity.&lt;sup>10&lt;/sup> For women with years left of working life, premature death from ovarian cancer means lost income and a heavy, unexpected financial burden on their families.&lt;sup>10&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Unique social burden of ovarian cancer&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Ovarian cancer affects women in all walks of life.&lt;sup>11&lt;/sup> For many women, a diagnosis can reshape a woman’s sense of self and their roles within family, community and society.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Ovarian cancer diagnosis often occurs during the years when women are caring for children, grandchildren, older relatives or when playing an active role in both their community and society, threatening the roles and relationships that may define their identity.&lt;sup>12&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>As highlighted in the report, this shift can cause significant distress for families, as women with ovarian cancer often move from being caregivers to becoming those in need of care.&lt;sup>13&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“Women who are struck down with ovarian cancer are frequently in the prime of their lives. We are working. We are mothers. We are looking after people, be it our own parents, our own children.” – Carolyn Groves, living with ovarian cancer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Mothers with an ovarian cancer diagnosis often worry deeply about how their potential loss of life could affect their children. For those who haven’t started or finished building the family they hoped for, there can also be distress about how treatment might impact their ability to have children.&lt;sup>14,15&amp;nbsp;&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“Five years survival for less than 50% of people is not good enough. While it’s five years of ‘living’, the reality is that ‘living’ equates to treatments, relapses, surgeries and feeling poorly for much of that time. Watching the fit and healthy ‘rock’ of our family turn into a skinny, pale, shadow of herself was the worst thing our family has ever experienced,” - Robyn Smith, Patient Advocate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Recommendations for a path forward for ovarian cancer in Australia&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/b>The report therefore calls on key stakeholders to:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Increase investment in research into risk factors of ovarian cancer and identifying early detection methods&lt;/b>. A proactive approach recognises the importance of both primary prevention strategies as well as early detection methods to maximise the chance of remission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Continue investing in health system initiatives that use precision medicine approaches for ovarian cancer treatment.&lt;/b> With the aim of improving effectiveness, increasing survival rates and addressing existing inequities.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Improve health equity regarding recruitment to clinical trials. &lt;/b>Focus on creating equitable pathways, inclusive of First Nations and Culturally and Linguistically Diverse (CALD) communities, for recruitment to clinical trials, as well as stakeholder collaboration to address language and cultural barriers.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Continue investing in supportive care programs that address the psychosocial needs of women with ovarian cancer, their families and carers.&lt;/b> Sustained support can reduce the psychosocial and socioeconomic burden of the disease and strengthen the health system across all stages of care.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Nathalie McNeil, Vice President and General Manager, AbbVie Australia &amp;amp; New Zealand, comments, “AbbVie supports ongoing collaboration to advance outcomes for women with ovarian cancer. We call on key health system stakeholders and decision makers to consider the recommendations presented in this important report.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“It’s our hope that Australia can improve its relative survival rates for ovarian cancer patients and reduce the overall socioeconomic burden on women, families, carers and the broader community impacted by ovarian cancer in the future.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Media&amp;nbsp;Contacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Rose Porter&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>We.&lt;/b> Communications&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;0493 980 176&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;rporter@wecommunications.com&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Fionnuala Hagerty&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;AbbVie&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;0422 767 605&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;fionnuala.hagerty@abbvie.com&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Issued by We. Communications on behalf of AbbVie Australia.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>About ‘The Value of Hope: Addressing the burden of ovarian cancer in Australia’ Report&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>This report was commissioned by AbbVie Australia and prepared by Deloitte. AbbVie provided input in relation to the report and its outcomes. The information for this report was sourced from published literature using publicly available data. Where information has been obtained from thirdparty sources, this is referenced. All costs are reported in Australian dollars unless otherwise stated. This report contains cancer data that is based on sex classifications (e.g., male and female), where ovarian cancer is classified as occurring within the female sex. Accordingly, this report refers to ‘females’ in incidence, mortality and survival reporting to reflect this convention, and ‘women’ elsewhere in the report. It is respectfully acknowledged that not all ovarian cancer patients may identify with this language.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>About AbbVie&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>AbbVie’s mission is to discover and deliver innovative medicines that solve serious health issues today and address the medical challenges of tomorrow. We strive to have a remarkable impact on people’s lives across several key therapeutic areas: immunology, oncology, neuroscience, eye care, virology and gastroenterology, in addition to products and services across our Allergan Aesthetics portfolio. For more information about AbbVie, please visit us at www.abbvie.com.au. Follow @abbvie on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/AbbVie&quot;>X&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/AbbVieGlobal&quot;>Facebook&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/accounts/login/?next=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.instagram.com%2Fabbvie%2F%3Fhl%3Den&amp;amp;is_from_rle&quot;>Instagram&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/AbbVie&quot;>YouTube&lt;/a> and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.LinkedIn.com&quot;>LinkedIn.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                                <separator
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-08T04:00:57.109-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T04:00:57.109-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/separator/v2/separator"/>
                                <title
                                    cq:styleIds="[1651545825694]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-08T04:01:03.911-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T04:08:24.835-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    jcr:title="References"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                    type="h1"
                                    variant="h"/>
                                <text_952717886
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-08T04:09:19.187-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T04:22:26.475-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>1 Momenimovahed Z, Tiznobaik A, Taheri S, Salehiniya H. Ovarian cancer in the world: epidemiology and risk factors. Int J Womens Health. 2019;11:287-299. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.2147/IJWH.S197604&quot;>https://doi.org/10.2147/IJWH.S197604&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;2 AIHW 2024, Cancer data in Australia, accessed from https://www.aihw.gov.au/reports/cancer/cancer-data-inaustralia/data&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;3 AIHW 2024, Cancer survival data visualisation, accessed from https://www.aihw.gov.au/reports/cancer/cancer-data-inaustralia/contents/survival&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;4 Cancer Australia, 2015, Lack of awareness of ovarian cancer symptoms, accessed from https://www.canceraustralia.gov.au/news/lack-awareness-ovarian-cancer-symptoms&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;5 Ovarian Cancer Research Foundation, About Ovarian Cancer, accessed from https://www.ocrf.com.au/ovariancancer/facts-about-ovariancancer&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;6 Richardson DL, Eskander RN, O'Malley DM. Advances in Ovarian Cancer Care and Unmet Treatment Needs for Patients With Platinum Resistance: A Narrative Review. JAMA Oncol. 2023 Jun 1;9(6):851-859. doi: 10.1001/jamaoncol.2023.0197. PMID: 37079311.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;7 Garzon S, Lagana A, Casarin J, Raffaelli R, Cromi A, Franchi M, Barra F, Alkatout I, Ferrero S, Ghezzi F 2020, Secondary and tertiary ovarian cancer recurrence: what is best management?, Gland Surgery 9(4), accessed from &lt;a href=&quot;https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7475365/&quot;>https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7475365/&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;8 Ovarian Cancer Research Foundation, State of the Nation Report, accessed from https://evenicoocrf2019.blob.core.windows.net/assets/pages/SOTN%20Executive%20Summary%20V1.2.pdf&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;9 AIHW 2024, Rural and remote health, accessed from https://www.aihw.gov.au/reports/rural-remote-australians/ruraland-remote-health&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;10 Hutchinson B, Euripides M, Reid F, Allman, G, Morrell L, Spencer G, Ilbawi A, Meheus F, Gaafar H, Casolino R 2025, Socioeconomic Burden of Ovarian Cancer in 11 Countries, American Society of Clinical Oncology, accessed from &lt;a href=&quot;https://ascopubs.org/doi/10.1200/GO-24-00313&quot;>https://ascopubs.org/doi/10.1200/GO-24-00313&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;11 Cancer Council NSW, 2023. 6 things to know about ovarian cancer. Accessed from: https://www.cancercouncil.com.au/news/6-things-to-know-about-ovarian-cancer/?utm_source&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;12 AIHW 2024, Cancer data in Australia, accessed from https://www.aihw.gov.au/reports/cancer/cancer-data-inaustralia/contents/cancerincidence-by-age-visualisation&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;13 Tan JH, Sharpe L, Russell H 2021, The impact of ovarian cancer on individuals and caregivers: A qualitative analysis, Psycho-oncology, 30(2), accessed from &lt;a href=&quot;https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32940943/&quot;>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32940943/&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;14&amp;nbsp;Arida JA, Bressler T, Moran S, D’Arpino S, Carr A, Hagan TL 2020, Mothering with ovarian cancer: “You’ve got to find that little thing that’s going to make you strong”, Cancer Nursing 42(4), accessed from &lt;a href=&quot;https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6111003/&quot;>https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6111003/&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;15 Laganà AS, La Rosa VL, Rapisarda AM, Platania A, Vitale SG 2017, Psychological impact of fertility preservation techniques in women with gynaecological cancer, Ecancermedicalscience, 8(11), accessed from &lt;a href=&quot;https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5336386/&quot;>https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5336386/&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                                <separator_2098848403
                                    cq:styleIds="[1662756456518]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-08T09:01:37.016-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T09:03:51.630-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/separator/v2/separator"/>
                                <text_1287306018
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-08T09:01:47.249-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T09:02:07.087-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>AU-ONCOC-250028. November 2025&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                            </par_12>
                        </grid>
                    </container_1286594283>
                </responsivegrid1>
                <experiencefragmentFooter
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-08T02:39:08.018-05:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/au/en/site/footer/australia-footer-english"/>
            </responsivegrid>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
