<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-22T13:41:08.598-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
        cq:template="/conf/abbvie-com2/settings/wcm/templates/story-landing-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-09T10:19:03.083-04:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="AbbVie welcomes Pharmac decision to widen access to VENCLEXTA® for New Zealanders living with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL)"
        jcr:uuid="0d246ff2-a2a9-4284-985e-02bed0214b66"
        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storypage"
        ctaAltText="Learn more"
        ctaText="Learn more"
        hideInNav="true"
        navTitle="AbbVie welcomes Pharmac decision to widen access to VENCLEXTA® for New Zealanders living with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL)"
        pageTitle="AbbVie welcomes Pharmac decision to widen access to VENCLEXTA® for New Zealanders living with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL)"
        publishDate="{Date}2026-04-09T03:04:00.000-05:00"
        readTime="3"
        readWatchTimeSel="read-time"
        title="AbbVie welcomes Pharmac decision to widen access to VENCLEXTA® for New Zealanders living with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL)">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
            <responsivegrid
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                <experiencefragmentHeader
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-22T13:41:08.592-04:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/nz/en/site/header/new-zealand-header"/>
                <responsivegrid1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                    <container1
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835859,1653545825683,1653545847150,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-21T04:04:43.868-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#071D49"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset"
                        enableFetchPriority="false"
                        enableLazyLoading="false"/>
                    <container2
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545835860,1653545825685,1653242825678,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#FFFFFF">
                        <container3
                            cq:styleIds="[1653545825686,1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                            <button
                                cq:styleIds="[1659997787459,1659997787460]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-22T13:38:17.194-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="All Media"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/button/v2/button"
                                accessibilityLabel="View All Stories"
                                langAttribute="none"
                                linkTarget="_self"
                                linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/nz/en/media"/>
                            <storyinfo
                                jcr:created="{Date}2026-04-06T16:05:02.004-04:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-06T16:05:58.843-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storyinfo/v2/storyinfo"
                                hideReadWatchTime="true"
                                hideTag="true"/>
                            <title_copy_copy
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1661545829678,1651545825691]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-08T18:40:51.104-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="AbbVie welcomes Pharmac decision to widen access to VENCLEXTA® for New Zealanders living with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL)"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                langAttribute="none"
                                type="h1"
                                variant="h"/>
                        </container3>
                    </container2>
                    <grid
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/grid/v2/grid"
                        rowCount="1">
                        <columns jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                            <item0
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item1
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="8"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item2
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                        </columns>
                        <par_12
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container4
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982,1653545825686]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                <text_copy_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-10-03T13:35:54.680-04:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-08T18:53:09.635-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    langAttribute="none"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>WELLINGTON NEW ZEALAND, 9 April 2026 – &lt;/b>AbbVie (NYSE: ABBV) welcomes Pharmac’s decision to expand access to venetoclax (VENCLEXTA&lt;sup>®&lt;/sup>)&lt;sup> &lt;/sup>for chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL) by funding two new treatment combinations from 1 May 2026&lt;sup>1&lt;/sup>.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>From 1 May 2026, Pharmac will fund two new combinations as first-line treatment options for eligible people with previously untreated CLL, venetoclax (VENCLEXT&lt;sup>®&lt;/sup>) in combination with ibrutinib and venetoclax (VENCLEXTA&lt;sup>®&lt;/sup>)&lt;sup> &lt;/sup>in combination with obinutuzumab.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>CLL is a type of cancer affecting white blood cells called B-cells, and may also involve the lymph nodes. In CLL, the B-cells multiply too quickly and live too long, so that there are too many of them in the blood.&lt;sup>2&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Many people with CLL have no early symptoms. Those who do develop signs and symptoms may experience enlarged lymph nodes, fatigue, fever, night sweats, weight loss and frequent infections.&lt;sup>3&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>CLL is the most common type of leukaemia in New Zealand, with approximately 300 people diagnosed every year.&lt;sup>3&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>AbbVie New Zealand Country Manager, David Manifold said the decision is a significant milestone for people living with CLL, their whānau, and the clinicians and advocacy groups who have worked for many years to improve access to innovative treatment options in New Zealand.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“A diagnosis of CLL can bring significant uncertainty for those diagnosed and their families. This decision means eligible New Zealanders will have access to additional first-line treatment options, improving choice for people with CLL,” Manifold said.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“We acknowledge the tireless advocacy of the patient community, including patient advocacy groups, healthcare professionals and everyone who contributed to the consultation. Their voices have helped highlight the unmet need for access to contemporary standards of care,” Manifold continued.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“Funding of treatments is an important step in improving equity of medicines access within the New Zealand health system. Continued focus is needed to ensure people with blood cancer can access timely, evidence-based medicines that reflect international treatment guidelines,” Manifold concluded.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Products will be listed on the Pharmaceutical Schedule from 1 May 2026 and eligibility restrictions apply. Ask your health professional if these products are right for you.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Important VENCLEXTA® (venetoclax) safety information&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>VENCLEXTA is a prescription medicine containing venetoclax. VENCLEXTA is available as film-coated tablets of various strength (10 mg, 50 mg, 100 mg venetoclax). It is used to treat adults with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL), small lymphocytic lymphoma (SLL) or acute myeloid leukemia (AML). VENCLEXTA is taken alone or in combination with other medicines. Your doctor will let you know which combination medicines, how to take them, and how long to take them. Typically, you will start treatment with VENCLEXTA at a low dose. If you are taking VENCLEXTA for CLL or SLL, your doctor will gradually increase your dose over 5 weeks up to the full dose. If you are taking VENCLEXTA for AML, your doctor will gradually increase your dose up to the full dose over 3, or 4 days, depending on the combination medicine used. Use strictly as directed by your doctor.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>VENCLEXTA has risks and benefits.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/b>You must not take it if you are allergic to venetoclax or to any of the inactive ingredients. For CLL or SLL, do not take VENCLEXTA if you are taking any of the following medicines: medicines used to treat or prevent fungal infections, including ketoconazole, posaconazole, voriconazole, itraconazole; clarithromycin (an antibiotic); or ritonavir (a medicine used to treat HIV and hepatitis C). Do not drink grapefruit juice, or eat grapefruit, starfruit or Seville oranges or marmalades. Do not give VENCLEXTA to children and adolescents under 18 years of age. Do not take VENCLEXTA if you are pregnant or plan to become pregnant, or if you are breastfeeding or plan to breastfeed. If you are a woman of child-bearing age, you must use a highly effective form of contraception during treatment with VENCLEXTA and for at least 30 days after your last dose. Tell your doctor, nurse, or pharmacist if you have any kidney or liver&amp;nbsp;problems; if you think you may have an infection; or if you recently received or are scheduled for any vaccinations. Do not stop using VENCLEXTA or change the dose without checking with your doctor.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>VENCLEXTA can cause tumour lysis syndrome (TLS)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>which is caused by the fast breakdown of cancer cells. TLS is a very serious side effect that can be fatal. TLS is most likely to occur when you are first starting treatment. To help prevent TLS, it is important to stay hydrated and drink water every day when taking VENCLEXTA. Particularly, starting two days before and on the day of your first dose of VENCLEXTA and every time the dose is increased, drink 6 to 8 glasses (approximately 1.5-2 L total) of water each day. Let your healthcare provider know immediately if you experience: fever or chills; feeling sick or vomiting; being short of breath; feeling unusually tired; changes in your heart rate (slow, fast or irregular); your urine looks dark or cloudy; feeling confused; convulsions or fits; or pain in the muscles or joints while on treatment with VENCLEXTA. Ensure you follow all your doctor’s instructions carefully and keep all your appointments, including those for blood tests. You may experience a low number of neutrophils, a type of white blood cells – this can be severe and need treatment. Your doctor will check your blood counts during treatment with VENCLEXTA. You may experience infections during treatment with VENCLEXTA. Some infections can be very serious or even fatal. Your doctor will closely monitor and treat you right away if you have fever or any signs of infection during treatment with VENCLEXTA. Tell your doctor immediately if you have signs of an infection before, or while taking VENCLEXTA, including: fever or chills, feeling weak or confused, cough, runny nose, sore throat; congestion on the chest; or pain or burning when passing urine.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Some of the less serious side effects of VENCLEXTA include diarrhoea; tummy pain; constipation, nausea (feeling sick); vomiting; reduced appetite; weight loss; mouth sores; looking pale; feeling tired; having little or no energy; shortness of breath when exercising; feeling dizzy; headache; low blood pressure; bleeding. Tell your doctor or pharmacist if you notice anything else that is making you feel unwell. Some medicines and VENCLEXTA may interfere with each other, so tell your doctor if you are taking medicines containing any of the following: ketoconazole, posaconazole, voriconazole, itraconazole, fluconazole, clarithromycin, ciprofloxacin, erythromycin, ritonavir, diltiazem, verapamil, captopril, felodipine, dronedarone, amiodarone, quinidine, rifampicin, carvedilol, ciclosporin, quercetin, ranolazine, ticagrelor, azithromycin, nafcillin, carbamazepine, phenytoin, St John’s wort (Hypericum perforatum), bosentan, efavirenz, etravirine, modafinil, warfarin, digoxin, everolimus, or sirolimus. Tell your doctor or pharmacist if you are taking any other medicines, including any medicines, vitamins or supplements that you buy without prescription. Tell any other doctors, pharmacists, dentists, or surgeons treating you that you are taking VENCLEXTA and remind them before you start any new medicines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;If you have any questions about using VENCLEXTA, including its risks and benefits, how much to use, how and when to use it, or storage conditions, ask your healthcare professional and refer to the Consumer Medicine Information (CMI) available from www.medsafe.govt.nz or free phone 0800 900 030. Ask your doctor if VENCLEXTA is&amp;nbsp;right for you. Use strictly as directed. If symptoms continue, or you have side effects, see your doctor, pharmacist, or healthcare professional.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>PHARMAC Pharmaceutical Schedule&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VENCLEXTA in combination with obinutuzumab or ibrutinib will be fully funded for untreated chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL) from 1 May 2026. VENCLEXTA in combination with rituximab is fully funded for relapsed/refractory CLL. VENCLEXTA in combination with azacitidine or low dose cytarabine is fully funded for acute myeloid leukaemia (AML). Special Authority criteria apply. Refer to the VENCLEXTA Pharmac Special Authority criteria &lt;a href=&quot;https://abbv.ie/NZ-Venetoclax-OnlineSchedule&quot; title=&quot;https://abbv.ie/nz-venetoclax-onlineschedule&quot;>https://abbv.ie/NZ-Venetoclax-OnlineSchedule&lt;/a>.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VENCLEXTA is supplied in New Zealand by: AbbVie Limited, L6, 156-158 Victoria Street, Wellington, 6011, New Zealand Tel: 0800 900 030. [MCMI Ver 7a]&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a name=&quot;_Hlk79676186&quot; id=&quot;_Hlk79676186&quot;>&lt;/a>&lt;b>About AbbVie&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/b>AbbVie’s mission is to discover and deliver innovative medicines that solve serious health issues today and address the medical challenges of tomorrow. We strive to have a remarkable impact on people’s lives across several key therapeutic areas: immunology, oncology, neuroscience, eye care, virology and gastroenterology, in addition to products and services across our Allergan Aesthetics portfolio. For more information about AbbVie, please visit us at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abbvie.co.nz/&quot;>www.abbvie.co.nz.&lt;/a>&lt;b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; Media:&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/b>AbbVie Corporate Communications ANZ&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;media_anz@abbvie.com&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>References&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ol>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Pharmac &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pharmac.govt.nz/news-and-resources/consultations-and-decisions&quot;>https://www.pharmac.govt.nz/news-and-resources/consultations-and-decisions&lt;/a>&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Venclexta Consumer Medical Information (CMI). Version 12. Updated 21 June 2024. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.medsafe.govt.nz/consumers/cmi/v/venclexta.pdf&quot;>https://www.medsafe.govt.nz/consumers/cmi/v/venclexta.pdf&lt;/a>&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Blood Cancer NZ, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloodcancer.org.nz/blood-cancer-information/chronic-lymphocytic-leukaemia&quot;>https://www.bloodcancer.org.nz/blood-cancer-information/chronic-lymphocytic-leukaemia&lt;/a>. Accessed April 2026&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ol>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>AbbVie New Zealand (AbbVie Ltd)&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;156-158 Victoria Street&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Wellington&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Date of preparation: April 2026&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Document number: NZ-VENC-260019&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;TAPS Approval number: BG6164&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                            </container4>
                        </par_12>
                        <par_13
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container5
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"/>
                        </par_13>
                    </grid>
                </responsivegrid1>
                <experiencefragmentFooter
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-22T13:40:41.435-04:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/nz/en/site/footer/new-zealand-footer"/>
            </responsivegrid>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
