<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-11T09:48:03.804-05:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
        cq:template="/conf/abbvie-com2/settings/wcm/templates/secondary-tertiary-page-template"
        jcr:description="Social channels allow us to share stories and information about serious health challenges around the world, plus news about our company.  Connect with us to get timely information about AbbVie and our areas of interest."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-11T09:48:03.788-05:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Social Media Community Guidelines"
        jcr:uuid="47cab806-9bab-405b-a36b-0e39c2a4c20f"
        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/remotepage"
        description="Looking for more news from AbbVie? Follow us."
        fileReference="/content/dam/abbvie-com2/images/people-in-conference-room.jpg"
        hideInNav="true"
        navTitle="Social Media Community Guidelines"
        ogimage="/content/dam/abbvie-com2/images/stories/immunologys-next-frontier/imm-innovation-article-hero.jpg"
        pageTitle="Social Media Community Guidelines"
        title="Social Media Community Guidelines">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
            <responsivegrid
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                <experiencefragmentHeader
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/us/en/site/header/master"/>
                <responsivegrid1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                    <container
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835859,1653545825683,1653545847149,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-07-17T11:38:17.062-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundImageReference="/content/dam/abbvie-com2/images/stories/immunologys-next-frontier/imm-innovation-article-hero.jpg"/>
                    <container2
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545835860,1653545847150,1653545835879,1653545825685]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#FFFFFF">
                        <container3
                            cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545847150,1653545835879,1653545835860]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                            <title
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1661545829678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-08-25T11:21:55.113-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="Social Media Community Guidelines"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                type="h1"
                                variant="h"/>
                            <text
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-08-25T12:16:46.252-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;light-font&quot;>&lt;span class=&quot;body-unica-32-reg&quot;>Looking for more news from AbbVie? Connect with us to get timely information about AbbVie and our areas of focus.&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </container3>
                    </container2>
                    <container_614517142
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545825688]"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2022-12-12T17:39:42.812-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-12-12T17:39:42.812-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                        <text_1864523356
                            cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                            jcr:created="{Date}2022-11-28T14:12:33.220-05:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2024-01-19T00:59:06.454-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="kumarvx60"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                            text="&lt;p>AbbVie’s global corporate social media channels are owned and managed by our corporate marketing team. We use these platforms to share stories about serious health challenges around the world, AbbVie’s innovative work, as well as AbbVie company and employer news.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>We welcome the opportunity to hear from you on these channels. If you tag us, comment on our posts, or send us a private message, please follow these Community Guidelines to ensure we provide you the best experience.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please remember that we work in a highly regulated industry with unique legal considerations. We cannot engage in sensitive topics or discussions about our products, other companies’ products, or treatment options. These discussions are best held in private with a health care professional.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Because of these regulations, discussions need to be on‐topic and constructive. For this reason, we may hide or not respond to mentions, direct messages or replies that:&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Name our or other companies’ products.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Offer health or medical advice.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Include profanity, defamatory, libelous, offensive, abusive, discriminatory, harassing, or demeaning content, including images, videos, and links.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Are disparaging, threatening, condone violence or illegal behavior.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Contain personal information, like the names of individuals, email addresses, phone numbers, personal photos, or videos.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Contain proprietary, confidential, sensitive, or non-public information.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Violate copyright or intellectual property.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Are commercial in nature with an intent to sell products and services, or recruit fans and followers to other social communities.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Contain information that is false, inaccurate, or misleading.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;li>Are excessively repetitive and/or disruptive to the community (SPAM); or violate the platform terms.&lt;/li>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Accounts that AbbVie follows and content that AbbVie favorites or retweets are not an indication of AbbVie’s endorsement of these accounts or the content they produce. Nor is it an indication that we are engaged in a business relationship with the content authors. AbbVie is not responsible for and does not assume any liability for any such third-party content. AbbVie is not responsible for the terms and conditions, privacy policy or content of any website accessed through links or references in our social media posts. Any information expressed by AbbVie is subject to the risk factors and information on forward‐looking statements contained in its filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission and available at AbbVie.com. Nothing provided on these channels constitutes an offer or invitation to invest or deal in AbbVie securities.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Medical side effects&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If you believe you have experienced any medical side effects from an AbbVie product, please consult your physician, pharmacist, or other healthcare professional immediately. You can report this, a product issue or product question to us directly by using the &lt;a href=&quot;/content/abbvie-com2/us/en/contactus.html&quot;>medical information form&lt;/a> found on AbbVie.com.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>We suggest you avoid sharing specific information concerning your personal health on social media sites and the Internet in general. If you decide to direct message us to detail any side effects or report a complaint, we may contact you for more information, such as your email address and phone number, in order to assist you.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Using and storing personal identifying information&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>AbbVie will not disclose or share personal identifying information on its social channels unless we have obtained proper consents. We do not store or use your profile unique ID, email, or other personal identifying information. However, in the case of reporting a side effect or product issue, we will need to store and use personal identifying information, such as your name, location, health‐related information or similar, in accordance with applicable laws and for auditing purposes. This information is required to be submitted to the AbbVie Pharmacovigilance and Patient Safety department and/or regulatory authorities.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>In some instances, AbbVie may choose to use third‐party service providers to help us manage comments and messages, which means that they too would have access to any personal identifying information you share with us. Such third‐party service providers are contractually bound and trained to ensure adequate protection and security of your personal identifying information.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Thank you for following us, and we look forward to connecting with you on our social channels.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                            textIsRich="true"/>
                        <separator
                            cq:styleIds="[1662756486159]"
                            jcr:created="{Date}2022-12-12T17:45:31.536-05:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-12-12T17:45:31.536-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/separator/v2/separator"/>
                        <accordion
                            cq:styleIds="[1]"
                            jcr:created="{Date}2022-11-28T17:20:34.179-05:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2024-01-19T01:08:44.844-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="kumarvx60"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/accordion/v2/accordion"
                            heading="Additional information"
                            headingElement="h5"
                            singleExpansion="false">
                            <item_1670884293427
                                cq:panelTitle="LinkedIn"
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-08-25T11:20:48.882-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>Please review&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/legal/user-agreement?trk=hb_ft_userag&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>LinkedIn’s User Agreement&lt;/a> for additional information around the type of conversation that is allowed on this platform.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please be aware that followers who violate the above rules may be blocked from our LinkedIn page. In this case, the user would no longer be able to follow our news or comment on our posts.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please note that LinkedIn also has access to information you share with us. For more details read the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb_ft_priv&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>LinkedIn Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                            <item_1670884289120
                                cq:panelTitle="Facebook"
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-08-25T11:20:55.419-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>Review &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/policies_center/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Facebook’s terms and policies&lt;/a> for additional information on the type of conversation that is allowed on this platform.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please be aware that followers who violate the above rules may be blocked from our Facebook page. In this case, the user would no longer be able to follow our news or comment on our post.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please note that Facebook also has access to information you share with us. For more details please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policy/?entry_point=data_policy_redirect&amp;amp;entry=0&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Facebook’s Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                            <item_1689606506159
                                cq:panelTitle="Instagram"
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-08-25T11:21:04.329-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>Please review &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.instagram.com/581066165581870?helpref=page_content&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Instagram’s terms and policies&lt;/a> for additional information on the type of conversation that is allowed on this platform.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please be aware that followers who violate the above rules may be blocked from our Instagram account. In this case, the user would no longer be able to follow our news or comment on our posts.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please note that Instagram also has access to information you share with us. For more details please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://privacycenter.instagram.com/policy/?entry_point=ig_help_center_data_policy_redirect&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Instagram’s Data and Privacy Policy.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                            <item_1670884282434
                                cq:panelTitle="X (formerly Twitter)"
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-08-25T11:21:08.967-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>Due to the nature of this platform, if you do not follow our account and decide to mention us to detail any side effects or report a complaint, we may reach out to ask that you follow @AbbVie in order to learn more.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Review X’s Platform &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/tos?lang=en&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Terms&lt;/a> for additional information around the type of conversation that is allowed on this platform.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please be aware that those who violate the rules outlined in our community guidelines may have their replies hidden, tweets reported, or be blocked on our X account. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please note that X also has access to information you share with us. For more details please refer to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>X Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.&lt;br />&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                            <item_1670884286461
                                cq:panelTitle="TikTok"
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2024-01-19T01:08:31.609-05:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="kumarvx60"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>Review TikTok’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/us/terms-of-service/en&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Terms of Service&lt;/a> for additional information around the type of conversation that is allowed on this platform.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please be aware that followers who violate the above rules may be blocked from our TikTok account. In this case, the user would no longer be able to follow our videos or comment on our posts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please note that TikTok also has access to information you share with us. For more details, please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/us/privacy-policy/en&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>TikTok’s Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                            <item_1689606498683
                                cq:panelTitle="Glassdoor"
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2023-08-25T11:21:26.413-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>Please review Glassdoor’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.glassdoor.com/about/terms/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>terms&lt;/a> for additional information on the type of conversation that is allowed on this platform.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please be aware that anyone who violates the above rules may be blocked from our Glassdoor page.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Please note that Glassdoor also has access to information you share with us. For more details, please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;https://hrtechprivacy.com/brands/glassdoor#privacypolicy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Glassdoor’s Privacy Policy.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </accordion>
                    </container_614517142>
                </responsivegrid1>
                <experiencefragmentFooter
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/us/en/site/footer/master"/>
            </responsivegrid>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
