<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-23T10:00:55.651-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
        cq:tags="[abbvie-com-2:categories/working-at-abbvie-stories]"
        cq:template="/conf/abbvie-com2/settings/wcm/templates/story-landing-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-23T10:00:55.629-04:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Celebrating AbbVies 2025 Working Parents Caregivers"
        jcr:uuid="0796accf-49d1-4b6e-a96e-b3f8f0eabc65"
        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storypage"
        description="This year, AbbVie is honoring two working caregivers who embody lives of service while caring for family members and building thriving careers. "
        fileReference="/content/dam/abbvie-com2/images/stories/2025-working-parents/working-parents-hero.jpg"
        hideInNav="true"
        navTitle="Celebrating AbbVies Working Parents Caregivers"
        pageTitle="Celebrating AbbVies Working Parents Caregivers"
        publishDate="{Date}2025-09-23T11:32:00.000-05:00"
        readTime="4"
        readWatchTimeSel="read-time"
        title="Care and Commitment: Celebrating AbbVie's 2025 Working Parents/Caregivers">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
            <responsivegrid
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                <experiencefragmentHeader
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/us/en/site/header/master"/>
                <responsivegrid1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                    <container1
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835859,1653545825683,1653545847148,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-19T10:07:17.550-04:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundImageReference="/content/dam/abbvie-com2/images/stories/2025-working-parents/working-parents-hero.jpg"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset"/>
                    <container2
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545825685,1653242825678,1653545835860]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#FFFFFF">
                        <container3
                            cq:styleIds="[1653545825686,1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835879,1653545835982]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                            <button
                                cq:styleIds="[1659997787459,1659997787460]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:03:41.679-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="All Stories"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/button/v2/button"
                                accessibilityLabel="View All Stories"
                                linkTarget="_self"
                                linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/us/en/who-we-are/our-stories"/>
                            <storyinfo
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storyinfo/v2/storyinfo"/>
                            <title
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T12:34:58.994-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="Care and Commitment: Celebrating AbbVie's 2025 Working Parents/Caregivers"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                type="h1"
                                variant="h"/>
                            <text
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1659545835858]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T12:35:15.889-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;light-font&quot;>&lt;span class=&quot;body-unica-32-reg&quot;>This year, AbbVie is honoring two working caregivers who embody lives of service while caring for family members and building thriving careers.&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </container3>
                    </container2>
                    <grid
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/grid/v2/grid"
                        rowCount="1">
                        <columns jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                            <item0
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item1
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="8"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item2
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                        </columns>
                        <par_12
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container4
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545825687,1653545835982]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                <title2_copy_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678,1651545825692]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:05:03.224-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    jcr:title="Meet our 2025 Working Caregivers of the Year"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                    type="h2"
                                    variant="h"/>
                                <text2_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1659545835858]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:05:23.861-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>Our 2025 Working Caregivers of the Year, Anne Johnson and Donna Hahn, bring their best to AbbVie while caring for family members with illness and challenges – all with poise and grace.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Anne, a principal medical writer, joined AbbVie in 2023. Anne has a son with a severe disability – a rare genetic epilepsy disorder. The pride in her voice is evident when she describes her son. But she is modest about her efforts in balancing her work, caring for her son and her work in advocating and educating others about her son’s disorder.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Donna, a senior manager in Business Technology Solutions (BTS) quality assurance, wears many hats. She’s an experienced professional and mother/advisor/confidant to her young adult children. She is also the primary caregiver for her husband, who has been battling chronic neurological Lyme disease and mold toxicity for several years. In addition, her elderly parents, who reside at an assisted living facility, rely on her assistance with regular visits and ongoing emotional encouragement. Balancing these dual caregiving responsibilities places significant demands on her time and energy, underscoring her deep commitment to her family's well-being across multiple generations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                                <separator
                                    cq:styleIds="[1662756423318]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-09-17T13:17:32.554-04:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:17:32.554-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/separator/v2/separator"/>
                                <title2_copy_copy_cop
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678,1651545825668]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:17:27.736-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    jcr:title="Q: Tell us more about you. What’s your role at AbbVie? What’s your family situation? "
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                    type="h5"
                                    variant="h"/>
                                <text2_copy_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1659545835858]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:17:57.972-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Anne: &lt;/b>I joined AbbVie two years ago but have worked as a medical writer since 2016, including at my previous company, which focused on rare diseases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>I’m a single mom by choice. I realized I desperately wanted to be a mom but there was no one with whom I saw sharing my life. I knew I could provide a loving home on my own. I didn’t make this decision lightly. My son was my miracle and was very wanted.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>But there were signs something might not be right during the pregnancy – call it mother’s intuition. He was in the same breach position for the entire pregnancy, and I experienced some complications. He was born early, at 37 weeks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Even though he seemed healthy at birth, there were some signs that things weren’t right. He had trouble feeding and had a high bilirubin count. There were other things, too. He rolled his eyes as a baby and wasn’t reaching any of his milestones. I tried not to worry, but when we reached the 7-month mark, his daycare providers pulled me aside and shared their concerns. I followed up with the pediatrician and began a whole path of testing – MRIs, genetics and with a neurologist. I thought something was wrong from a neurological perspective, but the neurologist didn’t see it.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Eventually a dear friend said, “Anne, I think he’s having seizures.” Finally, a doctor ordered an EEG and determined he had constant seizures including infantile spasms. Then it took more time to get the genetic testing done. When he was 18 months, we had a diagnosis of STXBP1, but at that time little was known and what was known was frightening. While it was a relief to have a diagnosis, the journey was just beginning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Donna: &lt;/b>I’ve been with the company for six years. Throughout my time here, AbbVie has consistently offered valuable opportunities for skill development and career growth. I began my journey in software quality, transitioned into an operations role within security and risk management and then returned to software quality as a manager. These experiences have allowed me to broaden my expertise and advance my career within the organization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>My daughter is a recent college graduate and in her first professional role. My son is a rising junior in college for Electrical/Computer Engineering. My husband is no longer able to work due to disability. He has some cognitive and physical limitations, so I have taken over the household finances and care while he focuses on his health, medications and appointments. I'm grateful to have my parents living close by in an assisted living community for medical care and socialization. Both of them have health challenges as well.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                            </container4>
                            <quote_copy_copy
                                cq:styleIds="[1000000000000]"
                                jcr:created="{Date}2024-10-10T11:59:57.265-04:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-19T10:09:57.030-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/quote"
                                attributionName="Anne Johnson"
                                attributionTitle="2025 AbbVie Working Caregiver of the Year"
                                bgImageModifiers="resMode=sharp2&amp;op_sharpen=1"
                                dmPresetType="imagePreset"
                                fileReference="/content/dam/abbvie-com2/images/stories/2025-working-parents/anne-johnson-headshot.jpg"
                                imageModifiers="resMode=sharp2&amp;op_sharpen=1"
                                quote="AbbVie provides a collaborative environment, a community where we help each other. That makes the challenging times more manageable."
                                quoteType="regular"
                                textSize="h0"/>
                            <container4_copy
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545825687,1653545835982]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                <title2_copy_copy_cop
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678,1651545825668]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:18:44.977-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    jcr:title="Q: You have taken on significant roles to help others outside of your daily work and your caregiving roles. How are you involved in the community? "
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                    type="h5"
                                    variant="h"/>
                                <text2_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1659545835858]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-19T15:41:22.808-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Anne: &lt;/b>When my son was diagnosed, I decided to start a foundation. This was based on strong recommendations from my son’s neurologist and a friend. I connected with experts on genetics and epilepsy to reach this goal. One of my childhood friends, an ALS researcher, provided advice and made connections at Stanford to help me avoid pitfalls.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>With guidance and financial support from my friends and family, I created the infrastructure for the STXBP1 Foundation, becoming its founding president. I coped with grief by remaining busy. We attracted great people to work on the&amp;nbsp;STXBP1 gene and to join the foundation. We raised about $50,000 in a few months for Children’s Hospital of Pennsylvania (CHOP), started the first STXBP1 natural history study and created the first disease registry (100+ patients in the first 2 years).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>I organized the first STXBP1 conference, applied for grants to fund the event, and fostered excitement and collaboration among scientists and families. I aimed for young and passionate junior scientists to present their findings directly to families to inspire a bond to our organization and to deepen their commitment to STXBP1 research. My attendance at conferences allowed me to initiate valuable conversations, including one for a drug repurposing study with a Cornell researcher. This conversation eventually led to a Phase 1 4PB Study, where I was able to contribute my protocol expertise and to secure free medication via an investigator-initiated trial application, which we secured with help from the researcher.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>This journey was a convergence of my professional skills, personal connections and passion for advancing research and hope in rare diseases. When I passed the baton to another board member, I felt good about the legacy I left for the community.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Donna: &lt;/b>It’s important to have something outside of work that gives you fulfillment. For more than 14 years, I’ve been active in my church by teaching religious formation activities to help young people explore their faith. Having been with my students from first grade all the way through 10th grade, I’ve witnessed their growth and development firsthand. Serving as their teacher and a sounding board has allowed me to guide and support them in their faith and personal lives. Being part of their spiritual formation is a responsibility and a privilege I truly cherish.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>I’m also involved in various programs that promote mental well-being, including the nonprofit organization Peace of Mind Funding, which offers resources to those in need. I volunteer for various causes, including mental health awareness charities, golf outings, and clothing and food drives, showing my commitment to supporting wellness initiatives and community service.&amp;nbsp; When my children were younger, I volunteered at their schools to help create a safe and enriching learning environment for all students.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                            </container4_copy>
                            <quote_copy_copy_copy
                                cq:styleIds="[1000000000000]"
                                jcr:created="{Date}2024-10-10T11:59:57.265-04:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-19T10:09:44.667-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/quote"
                                attributionName="Donna Hahn"
                                attributionTitle="2025 AbbVie Working Caregiver of the Year"
                                bgImageModifiers="resMode=sharp2&amp;op_sharpen=1"
                                dmPresetType="imagePreset"
                                fileReference="/content/dam/abbvie-com2/images/stories/2025-working-parents/dona-hahn.jpg"
                                imageModifiers="resMode=sharp2&amp;op_sharpen=1"
                                quote="We’re so lucky at AbbVie to have such a strong culture, as well as benefits and resources."
                                quoteType="regular"
                                textSize="h0"/>
                            <container4_copy_copy
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545825687,1653545835982]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                <title2_copy_copy_cop
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678,1651545825668]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:20:24.329-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    jcr:title="Q: How does AbbVie help you be more effective at work and at home? "
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                    type="h5"
                                    variant="h"/>
                                <text2_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1659545835858]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:20:52.850-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Anne: &lt;/b>I feel very supported by AbbVie. During the first time my son was hospitalized after joining AbbVie, my manager urged me not to focus on work, which reduced my stress. We do important work that needs to get done on specific timelines, but knowing my colleagues had my back made a big difference.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>AbbVie provides a collaborative environment, a community where we help each other. That makes the challenging times more manageable. Flexibility to work from home has been pivotal, especially as my son has grown older and needs more support due to his quadriplegia. His increased size and weight make caregiving more demanding, but being home allows me to assist with lifting and available for urgent needs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Taking care of myself is intertwined with taking care of him. Bodybuilding became essential for physically managing his care, and I found a balance that benefits both of us. Though downtime is scarce, the situation is markedly better now, thanks to the support systems at AbbVie and the adaptability offered through AbbVie’s hybrid work model.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Donna: &lt;/b>AbbVie offers tremendous support in helping me be more effective both at work and at home. The caregivers circle through the Ability at AbbVie employee resource group (ERG) has been invaluable. The group provides a space to share ideas and benefits related to caregiving for children and elder care. In addition, they offer access to guest speakers who speak on various topics, including AbbVie’s benefits and resources. I’m also a member of the Veterans ERG, which allows me to connect with others who understand and appreciate the contributions of veterans, like my Navy veteran father.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>AbbVie’s caregiver leave allows for the opportunity of paid leave to care for a loved one, which was particularly helpful when my dad was in the hospital. The support AbbVie offers through the program, and the ease of accessing it with a simple app, makes juggling responsibilities much more manageable. It allowed me to focus on caregiving without feeling guilty or stressed about work. My manager further supports this balance, which reinforces AbbVie’s genuine commitment to fostering a culture that prioritizes work-life effectiveness, inclusion and professional growth. The company offers a wide range of resources and benefits designed to support employees in all aspects of their personal and professional lives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                                <title2_copy_copy_cop_494916771
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678,1651545825668]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:21:11.461-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    jcr:title="Q: Do you have any words of guidance or support that you’d like to share with others?  "
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                    type="h5"
                                    variant="h"/>
                                <text2_copy_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1659545835858]"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-17T13:21:45.552-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Anne: &lt;/b>A few things come to mind. First, find your community, your support structure – people you trust. Family is my biggest source of support, and I’ve built some strong relationships with my neighbors. I know I’m lucky. If I need help, there are always four or five people who will say, “I can help.” Second, make time for yourself – go for a walk, to meditate, get a massage, whatever is helpful for you. The third is to pace yourself if you decide, like I did, to create an organization or foundation.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Donna: &lt;/b>It’s important to find the work/life balance that works for you and to make the most of the time you have with your children, parents and loved ones. Also, attitudes are contagious, so try to stay positive; find your joy or something that gives a sense of accomplishment either at work or at home. I echo finding ways to take care of yourself and your mental health – including taking advantage of resources your company offers. Taking care of yourself is not an act of selfishness – it is an essential part of maintaining your well-being and supporting others. By prioritizing your needs, physical health and emotional balance, you recharge and become better equipped to handle life's challenges and to help those around you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>We’re so lucky at AbbVie to have such a strong culture, as well as benefits and resources. At work, I am fully engaged and committed to delivering results. When I am away from work, I feel confident knowing that I am supported by my team and organization so that I can give my all to the people I care for.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                            </container4_copy_copy>
                        </par_12>
                        <par_13
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container5
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                <container_copy_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1653545835879,1653545835982]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2022-12-06T11:42:35.351-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-12-06T11:42:35.351-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                    <header
                                        cq:styleIds="[2]"
                                        jcr:created="{Date}2022-12-06T11:43:47.745-05:00"
                                        jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-12-06T11:43:54.816-05:00"
                                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/header/v2/header"
                                        eyebrow="Related content"/>
                                    <cardpagestory
                                        cq:styleIds="[1111111111110,1111111111112,1111111111117]"
                                        jcr:created="{Date}2022-12-06T11:44:10.383-05:00"
                                        jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-19T16:30:50.878-04:00"
                                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/cardpagestory/v1/cardpagestory"
                                        hideImage="false"
                                        linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/us/en/who-we-are/our-stories/abbvies-2024-working-parents-finding-purpose-in-adversity"/>
                                </container_copy_copy>
                            </container5>
                        </par_13>
                    </grid>
                    <container_823421802_
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545825683,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2022-11-28T14:56:48.309-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-11-28T14:57:10.019-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#F4F4F4">
                        <title
                            cq:styleIds="[1661545829678]"
                            jcr:created="{Date}2022-11-28T14:57:53.189-05:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-11-28T14:58:09.963-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            jcr:title="Related Content"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                            type="h5"/>
                        <grid
                            cq:styleIds="[0]"
                            jcr:created="{Date}2022-11-28T14:59:59.998-05:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-11-28T15:00:11.955-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="chiucx"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/grid/v2/grid"
                            rowCount="1">
                            <columns jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                                <item0
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    columnWidth="6"
                                    dataPriority="1"/>
                                <item1
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    columnWidth="6"
                                    dataPriority="1"/>
                            </columns>
                            <par_11
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                                <cardpagestory
                                    cq:styleIds="[1111111111110,1111111111113,1111111111117]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2022-11-28T15:00:21.839-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-22T13:25:57.185-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/cardpagestory/v1/cardpagestory"
                                    hideImage="false"
                                    linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/us/en/who-we-are/our-stories/new-microsite-clinic-brings-healthcare-to-chicago-southwest-side"/>
                            </par_11>
                            <par_12
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                                <cardpagestory
                                    cq:styleIds="[1111111111110,1111111111113,1111111111117]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2022-11-28T15:01:47.525-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="chiucx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-22T13:26:33.923-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/cardpagestory/v1/cardpagestory"
                                    hideImage="false"
                                    linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/us/en/who-we-are/our-stories/real-people-real-inspiration-joes-story"/>
                            </par_12>
                        </grid>
                        <separator
                            cq:styleIds="[1662756542862]"
                            jcr:created="{Date}2022-12-09T14:41:07.756-05:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="millicx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-12-09T14:41:07.756-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="millicx"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/separator/v2/separator"/>
                    </container_823421802_>
                </responsivegrid1>
                <experiencefragmentFooter
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/us/en/site/footer/master"/>
            </responsivegrid>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
