<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-08T14:04:25.172-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
        cq:template="/conf/abbvie-com2/settings/wcm/templates/story-landing-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-08T14:04:25.156-04:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="AbbVie welcomes PBS listing of VYALEV®"
        jcr:uuid="90ee1b58-5c04-461a-a34f-e19a5db662b5"
        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storypage"
        ctaAltText="Learn more"
        ctaText="Learn more"
        hideInNav="true"
        navTitle="AbbVie welcomes PBS listing of VYALEV®"
        pageTitle="AbbVie welcomes PBS listing of VYALEV®"
        publishDate="{Date}2025-08-25T01:36:00.000-05:00"
        readTime="1"
        readWatchTimeSel="read-time"
        title="AbbVie welcomes PBS listing of VYALEV®">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
            <responsivegrid
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                <experiencefragmentHeader
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-21T01:37:32.344-05:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/au/en/site/header/australia-header-english"/>
                <responsivegrid1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                    <container1
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835859,1653545825683,1653545847150,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-21T01:37:57.251-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#071D49"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset"
                        enableFetchPriority="false"
                        enableLazyLoading="false"/>
                    <container2
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545835860,1653545825685,1653242825678,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#FFFFFF">
                        <container3
                            cq:styleIds="[1653545825686,1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835879,1653545835982]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                            <button
                                cq:styleIds="[1659997787459,1659997787460]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-02-26T09:03:37.012-05:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="All Media"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/button/v2/button"
                                accessibilityLabel="View All Stories"
                                linkTarget="_self"
                                linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/au/en/media"/>
                            <storyinfo
                                jcr:created="{Date}2026-04-06T16:08:52.549-04:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-06T16:09:03.139-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storyinfo/v2/storyinfo"
                                hideReadWatchTime="true"
                                hideTag="true"/>
                            <title
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-08T14:04:17.710-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="AbbVie welcomes PBS listing of VYALEV®"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                langAttribute="none"
                                type="h1"
                                variant="h"/>
                        </container3>
                    </container2>
                    <grid
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/grid/v2/grid"
                        rowCount="1">
                        <columns jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                            <item0
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item1
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="8"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item2
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                        </columns>
                        <par_12
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container4
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982,1653545825686]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                <text_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-10-03T01:31:46.202-04:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-05T02:42:21.966-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;b>SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA, AUGUST 2025 &lt;/b>– AbbVie Pty Ltd (NYSE: ABBV) is pleased to announce VYALEV® (foslevodopa with foscarbidopa) will be available from&lt;sup> 1&lt;/sup> August 2025 on the Pharmaceutical Benefits Scheme (PBS) for the treatment of advanced Parkinson’s.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Parkinson’s progresses at different rates for people and is managed by oral medications or device-assisted therapies depending on the stage of the condition.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VYALEV® is a 24-hour infusion of levodopa-based therapy, administered subcutaneously or ‘under the skin’ assisted by a pump carried close to the body. It is indicated for the treatment of advanced idiopathic Parkinson’s in people with severe motor fluctuations despite optimised alternative pharmacological treatment. &lt;sup>1 &lt;/sup>With up to 219,000 Australians living with Parkinson’s and 30 people diagnosed each day,&lt;sup>2&lt;/sup> Parkinson’s is the fastest growing neurological condition and second most prevalent after dementia.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Ten per cent of people diagnosed with Parkinson’s are under the age of 45 and 18 per cent are of working age (&amp;lt;65 years).&lt;sup>3&lt;/sup> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Parkinson’s is an incurable, progressive, whole-body condition. It is characterised by symptoms like tremor, muscle rigidity, slowness of movement and difficulty with balance resulting from the loss of dopamine-producing brain cells. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>As Parkinson's progresses people experience increased motor fluctuations, difficulty swallowing, recurrent falls, abnormal involuntary movement (dyskinesia) and need help performing daily activities.&lt;sup>4&lt;/sup> &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>This can result in high rates of disability, financial insecurity and significant burden on carers.&lt;sup>5,6&lt;/sup> The exact cause of Parkinson’s is unknown, but can be triggered by a combination of factors, including environmental, genetics and ageing&lt;sup>.7&amp;nbsp;&lt;/sup>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Dr Victor Fung, Professor of Neurology and Motor Control at the University of Sydney and Consultant Neurologist at Westmead&lt;/b> commented, “As Parkinson’s advances, people experience a range of disabling motor and non-motor symptoms and it can become increasingly complex and hard to manage. Having access to a range of treatments that respond to the needs of people at the different stages of their Parkinson’s journey is essential for ensuring the best possible quality of life.”&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p> “Device-assisted therapies are a group of specialised treatments that should be considered as a management option for people with Parkinson’s whose symptoms are no longer able to be controlled with oral therapies. &lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>It’s important to recognise there is a learning curve in moving to a device-assisted treatment and health care professionals and people living with Parkinson’s need to work closely together throughout their journey with their illness. Providing ongoing education&amp;nbsp;and support, setting clear treatment goals and expectations, and working in partnership to meet needs and optimise outcomes are key considerations, along with ensuring the treatment approach is personalised for the individual.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Professor Carolyn Sue, Chair of the National Parkinson’s Alliance&lt;/b> welcomed the announcement, saying: “People with advanced Parkinson’s live with significant unpredictability and uncertainty every single day. As the condition progresses, they may become increasingly dependent on those around them to help manage daily living. This loss of autonomy can take a huge physical, mental and emotional toll.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;“While there is no known cure for Parkinson’s at the moment, symptomatic control and regaining one's sense of self are essential for improving quality of life. People living with Parkinson’s need access to a range of affordable treatments as their condition progresses and we are very pleased a new option is now available through the PBS.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Olivia Nassaris, CEO Parkinson’s Australia&lt;/b> said the decision reflects the important role the community has in shaping PBS priorities, saying: “Parkinson’s Australia has advocated for access to VYALEV® in Australia to ensure people living with advanced Parkinson’s have a wider choice of treatments that can help improve daily living. Throughout this process consumer voices have been vital in helping decision makers understand the impacts of living with Parkinson’s.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;“We are delighted the Australian Government has made this treatment affordable and available for the Parkinson’s community.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Nathalie McNeil, General Manager of AbbVie Australia, welcomed the listing of VYALEV® on the PBS by the Australian Government, saying: “Parkinson’s is unpredictable, disrupting the lives of not only the people living with it, but also their carers, family and community. AbbVie is fully committed to supporting the Parkinson’s community through investment in research and developing therapies aimed at assisting people navigating the progression of Parkinson’s. We thank the Australian Government for partnering with AbbVie to make these important treatment advancements available.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;The decision to prescribe VYALEV® should be made by an authorised healthcare professional in consultation with their patient.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>IMPORTANT VYALEV® SAFETY INFORMATION&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/b>VYALEV® therapy is only suitable for people who are levodopa-responsive. Treatment should be initiated and monitored under the supervision of a healthcare professional with expertise in the management of Parkinson’s disease. VYALEV® should not be used if the person is allergic to foslevodopa, foscarbidopa, carbidopa&amp;nbsp;or any of its ingredients. It should also not be used if the patient has narrow angle glaucoma, liver or kidney problems, conditions affecting the adrenal glands, an overactive thyroid or has a history of severe heart failure, acute stroke, or severe cardiac arrhythmia.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Side effects:&lt;/b> All medicines can have side effects and most are minor and temporary. However some side effects may need medical attention. The most common side effects are pain and redness at the infusion site, uncontrollable twitching, jerking movements, hallucination, fall, anxiety and dizziness. Ask your doctor or pharmacist if you have questions about side effects.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Precautions:&lt;/b> VYALEV® should be administered with caution to patients with severe cardiovascular or pulmonary disease, chronic wide-angle glaucoma, bronchial asthma, renal, hepatic or endocrine disease, or history of peptic ulcer disease or convulsions. VYALEV® is not recommended during pregnancy and while breastfeeding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Interactions:&lt;/b> Concomitant administration of antipsychotics with dopamine receptor blocking properties, particularly D2 receptor antagonists, should be carefully considered. Use of nonselective monoamine oxidase (MAO) inhibitors and selective MAO type A inhibitors should be discontinued at least two weeks prior to initiating therapy with VYALEV®.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VYALEV® Consumer Medicine Information is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://rss.medsinfo.com.au/ve/cmi.cfm?product=vecvya&quot;>here&lt;/a> and healthcare professionals can access the Product Information &lt;a href=&quot;https://rss.medsinfo.com.au/ve/pi.cfm?product=vepvya&quot;>here&lt;/a>.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;No compensation was provided to clinical and consumer spokespersons for their involvement in this media activity, and the opinions expressed are their own.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;About VYALEV®&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VYALEV® is a prescription medicine containing two active ingredients, foslevodopa and foscarbidopa. It belongs to a class of therapeutics known as dopamine precursors and is used to treat adults with advanced Parkinson’s. VYALEV® is administered as a continuous infusion under the skin using the VYAFUSER™ Pump. A doctor determines and adjusts the dose based on individual patient needs, and after training, a patient can self-administer the treatment.8&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VYALEV® works by increasing the amount of a chemical called dopamine, which the brain requires to work properly.8 For further safety information on VYALEV® please review the Consumer Medicines Information &lt;a href=&quot;https://rss.medsinfo.com.au/ve/cmi.cfm?product=vecvya&quot;>here&lt;/a> (for consumers) or the Product Information &lt;a href=&quot;https://rss.medsinfo.com.au/ve/pi.cfm?product=vepvya&quot;>here&lt;/a> for healthcare professionals.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;About AbbVie&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;AbbVie’s mission is to discover and deliver innovative medicines that solve serious health issues today and address the medical challenges of tomorrow. We strive to have a remarkable impact on people’s lives across several key therapeutic areas: immunology, oncology, neuroscience, eye care, virology and gastroenterology, in addition to products and services across our Allergan Aesthetics portfolio. For more information about AbbVie, please visit us at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abbvie.com.au/&quot;>www.abbvie.com.au.&lt;/a> Follow @abbvie_AU on Facebook, Instagram or our LinkedIn page.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Media:&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;AbbVie Corporate Communications&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;media_anz@abbvie.com&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                                <title_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1651545825694]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-10-03T02:10:40.151-04:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-10-03T02:28:02.246-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    jcr:title="References:"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                    type="h4"
                                    variant="h"/>
                                <text_1921900585_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-10-03T02:10:47.379-04:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-11-05T01:24:42.789-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>1. VYALEV® Product Information. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rss.medsinfo.com.au/ve/pi.cfm?product=vepvya&quot;>Link.&lt;/a> Accessed July 2025&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;2. Ayton, D. et al. Parkinson’s disease prevalence and the association with rurality and agricultural determinants. Parkinsonism &amp;amp; Related Disorders. April 2019: 61:198-202&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;3. Parkinson’s NSW. What is Parkinson’s? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parkinsonsnsw.org.au&quot;>https://www.parkinsonsnsw.org.au/what-isparkinsons/&lt;/a> Accessed July 2025&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;4. Varanese, S., et al. Treatment of advanced Parkinson's disease. Parkinson's disease vol. 2010 480260. 7 Feb. 2011, doi:10.4061/2010/480260&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;5. Lubomski M, Davis RL, Sue CM. Health-Related Quality of Life for Parkinson’s Disease Patients and Their Caregivers. J Mov Disord 2021;14:42–52&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;6. Martinez-Martin P, Skorvanek M, Henriksen T, et al. Impact of advanced Parkinson’s disease on caregivers: an international real-world study. J Neurol 2023;270:2162–73&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;7. Mellick, GD. Jan 2024. Ecosystem of Parkinson’s in Australia project. Part 2: Systematic Review. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parkinsons.org.au/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Ecosystem-of-Parkinsons-Part-2-2024.pdf&quot;>Link&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;8. VYALEV® Consumer Medicine Information. &lt;a href=&quot;https://rss.medsinfo.com.au/ve/cmi.cfm?product=vecvya&quot;>Link&lt;/a>. Accessed July 2025&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                                <separator_1377505542
                                    cq:styleIds="[1662756515133]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-05T02:42:43.200-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-05T02:43:43.491-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/separator/v2/separator"/>
                                <text_1195413187_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-05T02:42:52.749-05:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-05T02:43:29.749-05:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>AU-VYAL-250058&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                            </container4>
                        </par_12>
                        <par_13
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container5
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"/>
                        </par_13>
                    </grid>
                </responsivegrid1>
                <experiencefragmentFooter
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-21T01:44:25.880-05:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/au/en/site/footer/australia-footer-english"/>
            </responsivegrid>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
