<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-07T13:57:29.583-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
        cq:template="/conf/abbvie-com2/settings/wcm/templates/story-landing-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-07T13:56:31.577-04:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="AbbVie Australia celebrates 12 years of Great Place to Work® certification"
        jcr:uuid="bba32e68-9bf4-49db-b856-60e7d37e470b"
        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storypage"
        ctaAltText="Learn more"
        ctaText="Learn more"
        hideInNav="true"
        navTitle="AbbVie Australia celebrates 12 years of Great Place to Work® certification "
        pageTitle="AbbVie Australia celebrates 12 years of Great Place to Work® certification "
        publishDate="{Date}2025-07-22T13:30:00.000-05:00"
        readTime="5"
        readWatchTimeSel="read-time"
        title="AbbVie Australia celebrates 12 years of Great Place to Work® certification">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
            <responsivegrid
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                <experiencefragmentHeader
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-21T01:16:36.889-05:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/au/en/site/header/australia-header-english"/>
                <responsivegrid1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                    <container1
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835859,1653545825683,1653545847150,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-21T01:16:26.697-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#071D49"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset"
                        enableFetchPriority="false"
                        enableLazyLoading="false"/>
                    <container2
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545835860,1653545825685,1653242825678,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#FFFFFF">
                        <container3
                            cq:styleIds="[1653545825686,1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835879,1653545835982]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                            <button
                                cq:styleIds="[1659997787459,1659997787460]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-02-26T09:02:24.792-05:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="All Media"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/button/v2/button"
                                accessibilityLabel="View All Stories"
                                linkTarget="_self"
                                linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/au/en/media"/>
                            <storyinfo
                                jcr:created="{Date}2026-04-06T16:07:10.655-04:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-06T16:07:50.131-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storyinfo/v2/storyinfo"
                                hideReadWatchTime="true"
                                hideTag="true"/>
                            <title
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-07T13:57:29.577-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="VALENSX5"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="AbbVie Australia celebrates 12 years of Great Place to Work® certification "
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                langAttribute="none"
                                type="h1"
                                variant="h"/>
                            <text_copy
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-24T07:34:43.634-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                text="&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;light-font&quot;>&lt;span class=&quot;body-unica-32-reg&quot;>Thanks to Its People-First Culture&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </container3>
                    </container2>
                    <grid
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/grid/v2/grid"
                        rowCount="1">
                        <columns jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                            <item0
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item1
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="8"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                            <item2
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                columnWidth="2"
                                dataPriority="1"/>
                        </columns>
                        <par_12
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container4
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982,1653545825686]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                                <text_copy
                                    cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                                    jcr:created="{Date}2025-09-24T07:36:26.958-04:00"
                                    jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-09-24T07:57:24.543-04:00"
                                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                                    text="&lt;p>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Sydney AUSTRALIA, [23 July 2025] &lt;/b>– AbbVie (NYSE: ABBV) AbbVie Australia is celebrating its 12th year in a row as a certified Great Place to Work®, a milestone achievement that reflects the organisation’s commitment to putting people first.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;After being certified for the first time in 2012, this year’s certification reflects a consistent an unwavering focus on prioritising workplace culture as a critical imperative for both employee wellbeing and business success.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Recognising the achievement, AbbVie General Manager and Vice President Nathalie McNeil said there are core cultural tenets that unify employees, “We are driven by making a real difference in people’s lives whether that be patients, the customers we serve, our community partners and each other. Our culture is built on the belief that success is not purely defined by what we deliver, but also the paths we choose to take along the way. It is about recognising that results and behaviour are equally as important.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;“Not many companies can say they have achieved a Great Place to Work® certification 12 years in a row and every year since its inception,” said Nathalie. “In an industry built on innovation, our culture continues to evolve just as dynamically. Over the past 12 years, through industry change, scientific breakthroughs, and global challenges, our team has shown a resilience and commitment that continues to inspire me.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;“What makes me proud is that we are not standing still, we are continuing to learn from each other, to work more closely across teams, and to create a space where honest feedback is encouraged and valued. As we celebrate this remarkable 12-year milestone, we are focused on fostering a workplace where people are supported, enabling us to continue our evolution as a great place to work.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Ellen Qiu, General Manager of Allergan Aesthetics* ANZ, says one of the most rewarding aspects of this result, is seeing how employee feedback continues to shape the direction of the company’s culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;“Every time we ask for feedback, we take it seriously and consider it,” said Ellen. “That is something I deeply value about our culture. We are open to learning, we’re not afraid to adapt, and we genuinely want to do better, for our people, our customers and for the business. We are committed to listening and making meaningful progress. That is how we grow, by learning from each other and moving forward together.”&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;For Mel Pantano, who leads the Immunology and Specialty Care Value and Access team, the recognition is personal, “I’ve grown so much here, not just in my career, but as a person,” she said. Mel began her journey with AbbVie in 2013, at the company’s inception.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;“The opportunities I’ve had to develop, contribute to the community, take on new challenges, and work with inspiring and passionate people have shaped the professional that I am today. What really matters though, you’re not just building a career here, you’re making a difference every day,” she said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Franky Prochilo, Head of Marketing and Commercial Excellence, Allergan Aesthetics ANZ, said “At Allergan Aesthetics, I have experienced belief in my potential and it’s the fantastic mentorship along the way that has guided me and provided opportunities that have challenged me to grow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;“The focus on developing people means I’m not just building a career, I’m creating lasting impact,” he said.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>About Great Place to Work®&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Great Place To Work® Certification™ is the most definitive “employer-of-choice” recognition that companies aspire to achieve. It is the only recognition based entirely on what employees report about their workplace experience – specifically, how consistently they experience a high-trust workplace. Great Place to Work Certification is recognized worldwide by employees and employers alike and is the global benchmark for identifying and recognizing outstanding employee experience. Every year, more than 10,000 companies across 60 countries apply to get Great Place To Work-Certified.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&amp;quot;Great Place To Work Certification is a highly coveted achievement that requires consistent and intentional dedication to the overall employee experience,&amp;quot; said Sarah Lewis-Kulin, the Vice President of Global Recognition at Great Place To Work.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;She emphasised that Certification is the sole official recognition earned by the realtime feedback of employees regarding their company culture. “By successfully earning this recognition, it is evident that AbbVie Australia stands out as one of the top companies to work for in Australia, providing a great workplace environment for its employees.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>About AbbVie in Australia&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;AbbVie's mission is to discover and deliver innovative medicines and solutions that solve serious health issues today and address the medical challenges of tomorrow. We strive to have a remarkable impact on people's lives across several key therapeutic areas including immunology, oncology, neuroscience and eye care – and products and services in our Allergan Aesthetics portfolio. For more information about AbbVie, please visit us at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abbvie.com.au&quot;>www.abbvie.com.au&lt;/a>. Follow us on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/abbvieaustralia&quot;>Facebook&lt;/a>, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/abbvieaustralia/&quot;>Instagram&lt;/a> or our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.linkedin.com/company/abbvie&quot;>LinkedIn&lt;/a> page.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>For media enquiries please contact:&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/b> &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Sam Pearson Head of Corporate Affairs &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:%20sam.pearson@abbvie.com&quot;>sam.pearson@abbvie.com&lt;/a> &lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;0418 419 549&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                    textIsRich="true"/>
                            </container4>
                        </par_12>
                        <par_13
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/parsys">
                            <container5
                                cq:styleIds="[1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835982]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"/>
                        </par_13>
                    </grid>
                </responsivegrid1>
                <experiencefragmentFooter
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-21T01:21:21.809-05:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="nandivx5"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/au/en/site/footer/australia-footer-english"/>
            </responsivegrid>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
