<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-07T09:47:31.002-04:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
        cq:template="/conf/abbvie-com2/settings/wcm/templates/story-landing-page"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-06T10:39:57.974-04:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Multi-product agreement between AbbVie and Pharmac to benefit New Zealanders living with blood cancer and autoimmune diseases"
        jcr:uuid="080a8f97-1353-4da6-8693-cc6794047878"
        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storypage"
        ctaAltText="Learn more"
        ctaText="Learn more"
        hideInNav="true"
        navTitle="Multi-product agreement between AbbVie and Pharmac to benefit New Zealanders living with blood cancer and autoimmune diseases"
        pageTitle="Multi-product agreement between AbbVie and Pharmac to benefit New Zealanders living with blood cancer and autoimmune diseases"
        publishDate="{Date}2025-05-01T12:24:00.000+05:30"
        readTime="5"
        readWatchTimeSel="read-time"
        title="Multi-product agreement between AbbVie and Pharmac to benefit New Zealanders living with blood cancer and autoimmune diseases">
        <root
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
            <responsivegrid
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                <experiencefragmentHeader
                    jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-23T10:23:52.828-05:00"
                    jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/nz/en/site/header/new-zealand-header"/>
                <responsivegrid1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="wcm/foundation/components/responsivegrid">
                    <container1
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835859,1653545825683,1653545847150,1653545835879]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-23T10:24:35.061-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#071D49"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset"
                        enableFetchPriority="false"
                        enableLazyLoading="false"/>
                    <container2
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545835855,1653545835860,1653545825685,1653242825678]"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-15T15:28:49.515-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="bryanjx9"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container"
                        backgroundColor="#FFFFFF"
                        dmPresetType="imagePreset"
                        enableFetchPriority="false"
                        enableLazyLoading="false">
                        <container3
                            cq:styleIds="[1653545825686,1653545847150,1653242825678,1653545835879,1653545835982]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                            <button
                                cq:styleIds="[1659997787459,1659997787460]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-02-23T12:16:38.206-05:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="All Media"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/button/v2/button"
                                accessibilityLabel="View All Stories"
                                linkTarget="_self"
                                linkURL="/content/abbvie-com2/nz/en/media"/>
                            <storyinfo
                                jcr:created="{Date}2026-04-07T05:03:56.475-04:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-04-07T05:04:04.105-04:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/storyinfo/v2/storyinfo"
                                hideReadWatchTime="true"
                                hideTag="true"/>
                            <title
                                cq:styleIds="[1659545825678,1651545824678,1651545825691]"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2025-12-23T10:25:11.393-05:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                jcr:title="Multi-product agreement between AbbVie and Pharmac to benefit New Zealanders living with blood cancer and autoimmune diseases"
                                sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/title/v2/title"
                                type="h1"
                                variant="h"/>
                        </container3>
                    </container2>
                    <container
                        cq:styleIds="[1653545825687,1653545835982]"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2026-01-15T15:26:00.633-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="bryanjx9"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-15T15:26:00.633-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="bryanjx9"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/container/v2/container">
                        <text
                            cq:styleIds="[1659545825678]"
                            jcr:created="{Date}2025-12-23T10:27:14.285-05:00"
                            jcr:createdBy="singarx"
                            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-02-17T11:21:06.277-05:00"
                            jcr:lastModifiedBy="singarx"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/text/v2/text"
                            text="&lt;p>&lt;b>WELLINGTON, NEW ZEALAND, May 2025 – AbbVie (NYSE: ABBV)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>welcomes Pharmac’s decision to expand access to two AbbVie medicines from 1 May 2025.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Under the new multi-product agreement with AbbVie, more New Zealanders will have access to upadacitinib (RINVOQ®) and venetoclax (VENCLEXTA®) to treat a wider range of conditions.&lt;sup>1&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/sup>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Pharmac previously funded RINVOQ for rheumatoid arthritis. Under the new arrangements RINVOQ will now be able to be used earlier in the treatment algorithm for RA patients and will also be available to treat eligible patients with moderate to severe atopic dermatitis (eczema), moderate to severe ulcerative colitis and severe Crohn’s disease. VENCLEXTA was previously funded for a type of blood cancer called chronic lymphocytic leukaemia, and with the expanded arrangements announced by Pharmac this will now be accessible to treat newly diagnosed patients with acute myeloid leukaemia who are unable to have intensive chemotherapy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;sup>2&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Country Head Bronwen Marshall said the new agreement is a significant step forward for people living with these conditions who have not previously had access to these advanced therapies.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“The decision by Pharmac was informed through consultation with stakeholders, and negotiations with AbbVie to enable wider access for New Zealand patients,” said Ms Marshall.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>“AbbVie would like to thank everyone who took the time to provide feedback on Pharmac’s proposal to ensure these new arrangements align with the needs of the community.” &lt;sup>3&lt;/sup>&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;AbbVie looks forward to working with health professionals and the community to support high quality care and best practice management for these six conditions.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;sup>1 &lt;/sup>Pharma: Pharmac to fund medicines for blood cancers, inflammatory bowel disease, eczema and arthritis&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;https://www.pharmac.govt.nz/news-and-resources/news/2025-04-pharmac-to-fund-medicines-for-blood-cancersinflammatory-bowel-disease-eczema-and-arthritis Accessed April 2025&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;sup>2&lt;/sup> Pharma: Decision to widen access to medicines for blood cancer, inflammatory bowel diseases, eczema and rheumatoid arthritis https://www.pharmac.govt.nz/news-and-resources/consultations-and-decisions/2025-04- decision-to-widen-access-to-medicines-for-blood-cancer-inflammatory-bowel-diseases-eczema-and-rheumatoidarthritis Accessed April 2025&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;sup>3&lt;/sup> Pharmac: Proposal to widen access to medicines for blood cancer, inflammatory bowel diseases, eczema and rheumatoid arthritis https://www.pharmac.govt.nz/news-and-resources/consultations-and-decisions/2025-01- abbvie-bundle Accessed April 2025&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Products will be listed on the Pharmaceutical Schedule from 1 May 2025 and eligibility restrictions apply. Ask your health professional if these products are right for you.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Important RINVOQ® (upadacitinib) safety information&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;RINVOQ is a prescription medicine containing upadacitinib hemihydrate and is available as modified release tablets each equivalent to 15 mg, 30 mg or 45 mg of upadacitinib. It is used for the treatment of moderate to severe active rheumatoid arthritis, active psoriatic arthritis, active ankolysing spondylitis, active non-radiographic axial spondylitis, moderately to severely active ulcerative colitis and moderately to severely active Crohn’s disease in adults, and moderate to severe atopic dermatitis in adults and adolescents 12 years and older.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>RINVOQ has risks and benefits.&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Do not use RINVOQ if you have an allergy to any medicines containing upadacitinib or any of the other ingredients in RINVOQ listed in the Consumer Medicines Information (CMI). Do not take the medicine after the expiry date.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Before you use RINVOQ, tell your doctor if you have (or have had) allergies to any medicines, foods, preservatives or dyes; an infection or a history of infections that keep coming back; tuberculosis, or you have been in close contact with someone who has had tuberculosis; herpes infection (shingles); hepatitis B or C; cancer or at high risk of developing skin cancer; heart problems, high blood pressure or high cholesterol; smoked or are currently a smoker; liver problems; kidney problems; blood clots in the veins of your legs or lungs; unexplained stomach pain, have or have had diverticulitis or ulcers in your stomach or intestines, or are taking nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory medicines; recently received or plan to receive a vaccine (patients taking RINVOQ should not receive live vaccines); are pregnant or plan on becoming pregnant; or are breastfeeding or plan to breastfeed. You may need blood tests before you start taking RINVOQ, or while you are taking it. Tell your doctor if you are 65 years of age or older.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Tell your doctor as soon as possible if you notice signs of a serious infection such as: fever, sweating or chills, feeling short of breath, warm, red or painful skin sores on your body, warts (skin papillomas), feeling tired, muscle aches, blood in your mucous, diarrhoea/stomach pain, cough, weight loss, burning when you pass urine or passing urine more often than normal. Tell your doctor immediately or go to your nearest hospital if you take too much RINVOQ (overdose), even without discomfort or signs of poisoning.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Tell your doctor and other health care professionals if you are taking any other medicines, including any that you get without a prescription from your pharmacy, supermarket or health food shop. Some medicines may affect RINVOQ how well it works, or they may be affected by RINVOQ. Avoid food or drink containing grapefruit. Tell all doctors, dentists and pharmacists who are treating you that you are using RINVOQ.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Tell your doctor if you feel unwell while taking RINVOQ. The more common side effects of RINVOQ include; throat or nose infection; cough; fever; feeling sick in the stomach; weight gain;&amp;nbsp;cold sores; painful skin rash with blisters and fever; acne; swelling of the hair follicles; flu; anaemia; pain in your belly; fatigue; headache; rash/hives.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;If you have any questions about using RINVOQ, including the risks and benefits, how much to use, how and when to use it, or the storage conditions, ask your healthcare professional and refer to the Consumer Medicine Information (CMI) available from https://www.medsafe.govt.nz/Consumers/CMI/r/rinvoq.pdf or freephone 0800 900 030. Ask your doctor if RINVOQ is right for you. Use strictly as directed. If symptoms continue, or you have side effects, see your doctor, pharmacist, or healthcare professional.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>PHARMAC Pharmaceutical Schedule:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;RINVOQ is fully funded under Special Authority Criteria for the treatment of eligible patients with rheumatoid arthritis and will be fully funded under Special Authority Criteria for eligible patients with atopic dermatitis, Crohn’s disease and ulcerative colitis. Rinvoq is not funded for ankylosing spondylitis, non-radiographic axial spondyloarthritis and psoriatic arthritis. For these indications patient co-payment for this medicine and healthcare professional fees apply. RINVOQ is supplied in New Zealand by AbbVie Limited, L6, 156-158 Victoria Street, Wellington, 6011, New Zealand 0800 900 030. [MCMI Ver 12]&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Important VENCLEXTA® (venetoclax) safety information&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VENCLEXTA is a prescription medicine containing venetoclax. VENCLEXTA is available as film-coated tablets of various strength (10 mg, 50 mg, 100 mg venetoclax). It is used to treat adults with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL), small lymphocytic lymphoma (SLL) or acute myeloid leukemia (AML). VENCLEXTA is taken alone or in combination with other medicines. Your doctor will let you know which combination medicines, how to take them, and how long to take them. Typically, you will start treatment with VENCLEXTA at a low dose. If you are taking VENCLEXTA for CLL or SLL, your doctor will gradually increase your dose over 5 weeks up to the full dose. If you are taking VENCLEXTA for AML, your doctor will gradually increase your dose up to the full dose over 3, or 4 days, depending on the combination medicine used. Use strictly as directed by your doctor.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>VENCLEXTA has risks and benefits.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa; &lt;/b>You must not take it if you are allergic to venetoclax or to any of the inactive ingredients. For CLL or SLL, do not take VENCLEXTA if you are taking any of the following medicines: medicines used to treat or prevent fungal infections, including ketoconazole, posaconazole, voriconazole, itraconazole; clarithromycin (an antibiotic); or ritonavir (a medicine used to treat HIV and hepatitis C). Do not drink grapefruit juice, or eat grapefruit, starfruit or Seville oranges or marmalades. Do not give VENCLEXTA to children and adolescents under 18 years of age. Do not take VENCLEXTA if you are pregnant or plan to become pregnant, or if you are breastfeeding or plan to breastfeed. If you are a woman of child-bearing age, you must use a highly effective form of contraception during treatment with VENCLEXTA and for at least 30 days after your last dose. Tell your doctor, nurse, or pharmacist if you have any kidney or liver&amp;nbsp;problems; if you think you may have an infection; or if you recently received or are scheduled for any vaccinations. Do not stop using VENCLEXTA or change the dose without checking with your doctor.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>VENCLEXTA can cause tumour lysis syndrome (TLS)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>which is caused by the fast breakdown of cancer cells. TLS is a very serious side effect that can be fatal. TLS is most likely to occur when you are first starting treatment. To help prevent TLS, it is important to stay hydrated and drink water every day when taking VENCLEXTA. Particularly, starting two days before and on the day of your first dose of VENCLEXTA and every time the dose is increased, drink 6 to 8 glasses (approximately 1.5-2 L total) of water each day. Let your healthcare provider know immediately if you experience: fever or chills; feeling sick or vomiting; being short of breath; feeling unusually tired; changes in your heart rate (slow, fast or irregular); your urine looks dark or cloudy; feeling confused; convulsions or fits; or pain in the muscles or joints while on treatment with VENCLEXTA. Ensure you follow all your doctor’s instructions carefully and keep all your appointments, including those for blood tests. You may experience a low number of neutrophils, a type of white blood cells – this can be severe and need treatment. Your doctor will check your blood counts during treatment with VENCLEXTA. You may experience infections during treatment with VENCLEXTA. Some infections can be very serious or even fatal. Your doctor will closely monitor and treat you right away if you have fever or any signs of infection during treatment with VENCLEXTA. Tell your doctor immediately if you have signs of an infection before, or while taking VENCLEXTA, including: fever or chills, feeling weak or confused, cough, runny nose, sore throat; congestion on the chest; or pain or burning when passing urine.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;Some of the less serious side effects of VENCLEXTA include diarrhoea; tummy pain; constipation, nausea (feeling sick); vomiting; reduced appetite; weight loss; mouth sores; looking pale; feeling tired; having little or no energy; shortness of breath when exercising; feeling dizzy; headache; low blood pressure; bleeding. Tell your doctor or pharmacist if you notice anything else that is making you feel unwell. Some medicines and VENCLEXTA may interfere with each other, so tell your doctor if you are taking medicines containing any of the following: ketoconazole, posaconazole, voriconazole, itraconazole, fluconazole, clarithromycin, ciprofloxacin, erythromycin, ritonavir, diltiazem, verapamil, captopril, felodipine, dronedarone, amiodarone, quinidine, rifampicin, carvedilol, ciclosporin, quercetin, ranolazine, ticagrelor, azithromycin, nafcillin, carbamazepine, phenytoin, St John’s wort (Hypericum perforatum), bosentan, efavirenz, etravirine, modafinil, warfarin, digoxin, everolimus, or sirolimus. Tell your doctor or pharmacist if you are taking any other medicines, including any medicines, vitamins or supplements that you buy without prescription. Tell any other doctors, pharmacists, dentists, or surgeons treating you that you are taking VENCLEXTA and remind them before you start any new medicines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;If you have any questions about using VENCLEXTA, including its risks and benefits, how much to use, how and when to use it, or storage conditions, ask your healthcare professional and refer to the Consumer Medicine Information (CMI) available from www.medsafe.govt.nz or free phone 0800 900 030. Ask your doctor if VENCLEXTA is&amp;nbsp;right for you. Use strictly as directed. If symptoms continue, or you have side effects, see your doctor, pharmacist, or healthcare professional.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VENCLEXTA in combination with rituximab is fully funded for relapsed/refractory chronic lymphocytic leukaemia (CLL). VENCLEXTA in combination with azacitidine or low dose cytarabine is fully funded for acute myeloid leukaemia (AML). Special Authority criteria apply. Refer to the VENCLEXTA PHARMAC Special Authority criteria available at https://abbv.ie/NZVenetoclax-OnlineSchedule. VENCLEXTA in combination with obinutuzumab or ibrutinib is not funded for 1L CLL. For this indication patient co-payment for this medicine and healthcare professional fees apply.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;VENCLEXTA is supplied in New Zealand by: AbbVie Limited, L6, 156-158 Victoria Street, Wellington, 6011, New Zealand Tel: 0800 900 030. [MCMI Ver 7a]&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>About AbbVie&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;AbbVie’s mission is to discover and deliver innovative medicines that solve serious health issues today and address the medical challenges of tomorrow. We strive to have a remarkable impact on people’s lives across several key therapeutic areas: immunology, oncology, neuroscience, eye care, virology and gastroenterology, in addition to products and services across our Allergan Aesthetics portfolio. For more information about AbbVie, please visit us at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abbvie.co.nz&quot;>www.abbvie.co.nz.&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;b>Media:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;AbbVie Corporate Communications ANZ&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;media_anz@abbvie.com&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                            textIsRich="true"/>
                    </container>
                    <separator
                        cq:styleIds="[1662756423318]"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2026-01-15T15:27:28.587-05:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="bryanjx9"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2026-01-15T15:27:36.490-05:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="bryanjx9"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/separator/v2/separator"/>
                </responsivegrid1>
                <experiencefragmentFooter
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="abbvie-com2/components/experiencefragment"
                    fragmentVariationPath="/content/experience-fragments/abbvie-com2/us/en/site/footer/master"/>
            </responsivegrid>
        </root>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
